Wolf, Benjamin Additional Arbitration Files 5803
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 84-17 The City of New York vs. District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Added Duties. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 84-18 Westinghouse Elevator Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 2006, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 84-19 Organon, Inc. vs. International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers, Local 467, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Issues(two grievances): 1) Fringe Benefits--Past Practice and 2) Layoff--Temporary Employees. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-20 Carlton Prescription Center, Inc. vs. Allied Trades Council, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Disloyalty. AN, RC.
- 84-21 Manhattan Marine and Electric Company, Inc. vs. Local 888, United Food and Chemical Workers (UFCW), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. EX, AN, RC.
- 84-22 Precision Fabricators, Inc. vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Iron Workers (IABS+OIW), Local 455, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Issue: Layoff--Seniority. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-23 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline--Violation of Plant Rules; Working Conditions--Parking Privileges. EX, AN, RC.
- 84-24 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  RC. Cancelled at hearing.
- 84-25 Interdynamics, Inc. vs. Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), Local 29, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 84-26 United Telephone Systems vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 827, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 84-27 Wainrite Stores vs. United Food and Chemical Workers (UFCW), Local 888, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Theft-- Company Property. EX, AN, RC.
- 84-28 Holy Cross High School vs. Association of Catholic Teachers, Local 1776, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Issue: Recall--Failure To Recall. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-29 New York City Transit Authority vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association (PBA), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Classification of Jobs. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-30 Perth Amboy Coal Company vs. Local Union No. 866, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Issue: Vacation Pay- -Eligibility; Sick Leave and Sick Pay--Eligibility. AN, RC, A.
- 84-31 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- 84-32 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers Union, Local 146, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Issue: Seniority--Past Practice; Assignment of Jobs-- Seniority. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-33 New Jersey State Department of Corrections vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  RC. Cancelled (?).
- 84-34 New York State, SUNY at Oswego vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- 84-35 Kings Harbor Health Care Center vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 144, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- 84-36 St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- 84-37 Van Lear Containers vs. Chemical Workers Local 639, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  RC. Withdrawn
- 84-38 Blue Cross/Blue Shield of New Jersey vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 32, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- 84-39 United State Postal Service (USPS) vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Issue: Absences--Discipline, Excuses. EX, AN, RC.
- 84-40 Eastern Steel Barrel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America (USWA), Local 5262, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- 84-41 Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Carol Branker, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Issue: Discipline--Improper Maintenance of Records. EX, AN, RC.
- 84-42 State of New Jersey vs. Communications Workers of America, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- 84-43 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- 84-44 United Parcel Service (UPS) vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- 84-45 Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority vs. Local 1931, District Council 37, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- 85-(10)0 St. Mary's Hospital vs. Local 1199-J, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 85-(10)1 Trans World Airline, Inc. vs. Brenda J. Stitt, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Issue: Discipline--Unauthorized Use of Company Property. EX, AN, RC.
- 85-(10)2 New York City (NYC) Office of Municipal Labor Relations (OMLR) vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council (D.C.) 37, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 85-(10)3 Van Lear Containers vs. International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), Local 659, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 85-(10)4 New York City (NYC) Off-Track Betting Corporation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council (D.C.) 37, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Issue: Absences--Unauthorized. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- 85-(10)5 Numberall Stamp and Tool Company, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Woerders (IAMAW), District 15, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 85-(10)6 New York City (NYC) Office of Municipal Labor Relations, Department of Health vs. Local 1199, Drug, Hospital and Health Care Employees Union; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification. EX, AN, RC.
- 85-(10)7 New York State vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 85-(10)8 New York City (NYC) Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 211, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Improper Personal Conduct. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 85-(10)8 New York City (NYC) Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 211, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 85-(10)9 United State Immigration and Naturalization Service vs. American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), Local 1917, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 85-(1)10 Lederle Labs Division, American Cynamid Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), Local 111, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Issue: Layoff--Recall. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 85-11 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 85-12 United State Postal Service (USPS) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude-- Neglect of Duty. EX, AN, RC.
- 85-13 State of New Jersey vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 85-14 Hercules Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local No. 271, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Absences- -Discipline. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 85-15 United States Postal Service (USPS) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  3 Cases; Issues: 1) Insubordination--Discipline; Discipline--Leaving Plant Without Permission. 2) Improper Personal Conduct--Toward Supervisor. 3) Improper Personal Conduct--Negligence. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 85-16 State of New York, Department of Correctional Facilities vs. Security Unit Employees, Council 82, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness; Absences--Excessive. EX, AN, RC.
- 85-16 State of New York, Department of Correctional Facilities vs. Security Unit Employees, Council 82, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 85-17 Presbyterian Hospital vs. Licensed Practical Nurses and Technicians of New York, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 85-18 State of New Jersey, Marlboro Psychiatric Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Discipline. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 85-19 New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation vs. Committee of Interns and Residents, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 85-20 Bemis Bag, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local 1439, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- 85-21 State of New Jersey, Marlboro Psychiatric Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Opinions, Decisions, and Recommendations of the Impasse Panel or its individual members
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Sept
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Oct
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Nov
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York Hearing Transcript, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Union Exhibits Vol I (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Union Exhibits Vol I (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Union Exhibits Vol II (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Union Exhibits Vol II (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol I (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol I (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol II (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol II (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol III (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol III (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, City Exhibits Vol III (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Misc. Exhibits (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Legal, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  "Motion for Clarification"
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Arbitrator's Notes (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Supporting Documents (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Union's Post Hearing Brief
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Supporting Documents (Box 8, Folder 9)
  City's Post-Hearing Brief
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Supporting Documents (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Other Relevant Cases
- Firefighters' Association of Greater New York and The City of New York, Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 11)